<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on CCrashZer0</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on CCrashZer0</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Take Out The Trash: A CTF walkthrough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/takeoutthetrash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/takeoutthetrash/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Take out the trash is a boot2root style CTF challenge. Your objective here is to compromise a user account and then determine the best path to take in order to escalate your privileges to the root user and retrieve the root flag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to discover our point of entrance we will first need to do a little bit of recon. This can be done by using the tool nmap. It comes standard in most pen testing distros. The command I like to use is &lt;code&gt;nmap -sC -sV -T4 -A &amp;lt;IP&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. Based on the results, I can see this server has an FTP service running. It allows anonymous login, which should be our entry point.&#xA;The nmap results reveal an FTP server running with anonymous login enabled our potential entry point. So this should be the foothold that we have been looking for&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sudo Gone Wrong: Critical Linux Vulnerability Puts Root Access at Risk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/sudogonewrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/sudogonewrong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the world of Linux, if you want to do anything as the administrator, you would need to use the command &amp;ldquo;sudo&amp;rdquo;. This simple command possesses the power of a thousand suns and once used it will allow you to do anything with unfettered access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OK, well that might be an overexaggerating of the sudo command. However, according to a new security advisory from Rich Mirch at Stratascale&amp;rsquo;s Cyber Research Unit (CRU), there are not one but two critical vulnerabilities in Sudo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to design, develop, and print my first maker coin!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/maker-coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/maker-coin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A maker coin is a simple yet affected way to show off your creativity and design skills and with a little ingenuity it can easily become a networking opportunity. So when I decided to create my first maker coin I wanted to go about it a different way and see if I could leverage the power of AI to bring my idea to reality.&#xA;The first thing I needed to do was figure out the dimensions of my design. Surprisingly enough I had just the item laying around that I wanted to base my design on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Got Into Cyber security - An accident turn into a career!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/howigotintocybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/howigotintocybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the questions I get asked pretty often is: “How did you get into this line of work?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, if I’m being completely honest… it all happened by accident.&#xA;You see I’ve always had an interest in computers and loved figuring out how things worked, but cyber security was never really on my radar. Originally, I wanted to become a digital artist and design immersive, realistic levels for video games. For me this was my dream job.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/leanringtoblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/leanringtoblog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creating a blog has been on my bucket list for several years. When I was younger, I used to write on various sites about a range of different topics. It really was an outlet for me, a way for me to escape form the day-to-day and it allowed me to express myself freely, and without concern.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But here we are years later and I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten how to actually write a blog. Every time I try, I get stuck in this endless loop of perfectionism, obsessing over every sentence, every detail, until I lose all motivation I started with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Website — A Dream Turned Reality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/myfirstwebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/myfirstwebsite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m still wrapping my head around this. The fact that I’ve successfully deployed my own website. This has been a long-standing goal of mine ever since I discovered the world of cyber security. Well it is finally time for me to carve out my own little corner of the internet. A space where I can share my thoughts, document what I’m working on, and dive into the research I’m passionate about.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NovaspiritTech</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/novaspirittech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/novaspirittech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;February 4 was a day of silence and sorrow as I received the heartbreaking news that Don from NovaSpirit Tech had passed away after his battle with cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Though I never had the privilege of knowing Don personally, his channel played a significant role in shaping my journey as a maker. His passion, creativity, and willingness to share his knowledge helped me nurture and develop my own skills, both as a hobbyist and a professional.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I sit here looking at my website going live for the first time I am overwhelmed with the possibilities this could lead to. One of my goals has been to create a blog sites and write about my interest, but now I am faced with the overwhelming question of what to write about and will anyone read it. Well in times of doubt I am reminded of a quote from the movie Field of Dreams - &amp;ldquo;If you build it they will come.&amp;rdquo; and that is exactly what I plan on doing, I will build this blog up for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
