<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on CCrashZer0</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on CCrashZer0</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Root Me: TryHackMe Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/rootme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/rootme/</guid>
      <description>Try Hack Me - RootMe Link to heading A ctf for beginners, can you root me? Link to heading Reconnaissance Link to heading Scan the machine, how many ports are open? Here is the nmap scann commands that I am going to be using.&#xA;nmap -sC -sV -T4 -A -oN nmap/result &amp;lt;IP&amp;gt; Breakdown:&#xA;-A: do an extensive scan on these ports -sC: Scan with default NSE scripts. Considered useful for discovery and safe -sV: Attempts to determine the version of the service running on port -T4: speed of nmap scan is 4/5 (personal preference of mine) -oN: Normal output to the file normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounty Hacker: TryHackMe Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/bountyhacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/bountyhacker/</guid>
      <description>You talked a big game about being the most elite hacker in the solar system. Prove it and claim your right to the status of Elite Bounty Hacker!&#xA;Recon Link to heading After we have deployed the room let&amp;rsquo;s take the IP address and plug it into our web browser and see if anything comes up. It looks like we have a hit. Ok it looks like the maker of this room is a Cowboy BeBop fan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Happens: TryHackMe Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/githappens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/githappens/</guid>
      <description>Try Hack Me - GIT Happes Link to heading Boss wanted me to create a prototype, so here it is! We even used something called &amp;ldquo;version control&amp;rdquo; that made deploying this really easy! Link to heading Objective: Link to heading In this write up we only have one objective and that is to find the Super Secert Password.&#xA;Scanning, and Enumeration Link to heading The first thing that I am going to do after deploying the box is run an nmap scan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lian Yu: TryHackMe Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/lianyu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/tutorials/lianyu/</guid>
      <description>Try Hack Me - Lian_Yu Link to heading A beginner level security challenge&#xA;Objectives Link to heading Deploy the VM and Start the Enumeration. What is the Web Directory you found? What is the file name you found? What is the FTP Password? What is the file name with SSH password? user.txt root.txt Recon, Scanning, and Enumeration Link to heading Once the VM has been launched I am going to start scanning the box.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
