<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CCrashZer0</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/authors/ccrashzer0/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CCrashZer0</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/authors/ccrashzer0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About CCrashZer0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/images/avatar.png&#34; width=&#34;400&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA; &lt;!--This works... DO NOT CHANGE!--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hi,I’m CCrashZer0, you could call me a cybersecurity enthusiast, ethical hacker, mentor, and maker. My passions run deep and wide, whether I’m diving into security research, developing scripts, or exploring the world of 3D printing. I love getting my down into the nitty-gritty of a new challange.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m always on a mission to expand my knowledge and sharpen my skills. You’ll often find me in my lab, solving challenges on platforms like TryHackMe and HackTheBox — usually with a podcast playing in the background. But just as easily, you might catch me jamming to music while fine-tuning a 3D printer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/CCrashZer0/ccrashzer0.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I sit here looking at my website going live for the first time I am overwhelmed with the possibilities this could lead to. One of my goals has been to create a blog sites and write about my interest, but now I am faced with the overwhelming question of what to write about and will anyone read it. Well in times of doubt I am reminded of a quote from the movie Field of Dreams - &amp;ldquo;If you build it they will come.&amp;rdquo; and that is exactly what I plan on doing, I will build this blog up for all to see.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
